<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cecilia&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cecilia&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 19:55:25 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Homework 2</title>
      <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/posts/homework2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 19:55:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/posts/homework2/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone !
Lecture 2 : Homework The Ultimate Display form Evan E. Sutherland In this paper, Evan Sutherland points out the interesting 1960s&#39; displays, which will be developed in the future. On top of that, he even predicts new displays that we use today.
First, he reminds us about the importance of a display: understand digital computers as we understand the laws in a physical world.
Then, from the displays used in his area, he guesses the ones that will be mainly used in the future : the keyboards, the &amp;ldquo;area filling&amp;rdquo; ability, the stylus and its drag and drop ability, the knobs and the joysticks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 3</title>
      <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/posts/lab3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 16:10:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/posts/lab3/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone !
Today I build my Roll a Ball game on my Android phone.
Lab 3 Part 1 : Set up To build on Android I had to start with installing the Android Build Support :
()
Then, I had to define the new build settings, starting with the player settings : the orientation, the graphic APIs, the identification and the publishing key.
After setting up my unity project, I had to set up my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 2</title>
      <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/posts/lab2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 14:16:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/posts/lab2/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone !
Lab 2 Today, I built the 3D Unity Application : Roll A Ball. I followed the Unity learn steps to create it. I started by creating the ground :
Then my player :
I changed the light to have a better direction :
I changed the Input System Package :
I changed the Build Settings of my project. I had no errors, because I already had Visual Studio and Windows 10 SDK :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 1 : Homework</title>
      <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/posts/lecture1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 18:35:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/posts/lecture1/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone !
After creating my blog, it is time to write my first Human Computer Interaction&amp;rsquo;s assignment.
Affordances As I saw in class, an affordance is a property of an artefact which indicates its usage.
To illustrate this concept, I chose to talk about my vacuum cleaner. Its handle is well done. Automatically through its form, we know how to use the vacuum.
On the contrary, a bad affordance leads us to an incorrect usage of an object.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 1</title>
      <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/posts/lab1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 15:38:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Ceici92.github.io/HugoBlog3/posts/lab1/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone !
During my first lab of HCI, I learned how to make a blog with the static site generator Hugo, how to deploy it with GitHub, and how to setup a Unity project.
Part 1 : Setup my Blog First steps with Hugo It is my first blog, and my first time using a static site generator. For simplicity, I chose to use the one advised by my teachers : Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
